{
    "subject": "resource/Umayyad_Caliphate",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/Gold_dinar",
    "human_readable": "The currency of Umayyad Caliphate is Gold dinar.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9207543730735779,
            "question": "Besides Gold dinar, what other currencies were used in the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9087603688240051,
            "question": "What factors influenced the adoption of the Gold dinar as the official currency of the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.903385579586029,
            "question": "What was the currency of the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8470476865768433,
            "question": "Name the type of coin used as currency in the Umayyad Caliphate."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7931846380233765,
            "question": "What material was the currency of the Umayyad Caliphate made of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7828524112701416,
            "question": "Were there any variations in the design or weight of the Gold dinar issued by the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6816396117210388,
            "question": "How did the use of Gold dinar contribute to the economic stability of the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6002633571624756,
            "question": "During which historical period was the Gold dinar used as currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5142070651054382,
            "question": "How did the use of a standardized currency impact trade within the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45721471309661865,
            "question": "What was the value of the Gold dinar compared to other currencies of the time?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of Umayyad Caliphate is Gold dinar.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8944_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the use of a standardized currency impact trade within the Umayyad Caliphate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8944_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=During which historical period was the Gold dinar used as currency?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8944_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the use of Gold dinar contribute to the economic stability of the Umayyad Caliphate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8944_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8944_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8944_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8944_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8944_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8944_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8944_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8944_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8944_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8944_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8944_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to be evaluated is:\n\n\"The currency of Umayyad Caliphate is Gold dinar.\"\n\nHere's the structured JSON response based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\n\n* The context information mentions several times that the Umayyad Gold Dinar was a gold coin minted during the reign of Caliph Hisham ibn Abd al-Malik, indicating that it was indeed a currency used by the Umayyad Caliphate.\n* There is no mention of any other currency being used by the Umayyad Caliphate in the provided context information.\n\nTherefore, the statement \"The currency of Umayyad Caliphate is Gold dinar\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that gold dinars were a form of currency used during the Umayyad Caliphate, with specific details about the 723 Umayyad Gold Dinar. This directly supports the query that the Umayyad Caliphate's currency included gold dinars."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}